bezar.com 2015-10-20

# Privacy Policy | Bezar

_Last updated: January 6, 2015_

This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) describes how we collect, use and disclose information that we obtain when you visit our website at www.bezar.com (“Site”) and/or use our applications and services (collectively, “Services”). As used in this Policy, the terms “Bezar”, “we”, “us”, “our” and the like refer to Bezar, Inc., a Delaware corporation, and the terms “you”, “your” and the like refer to you, the end-user of our Site and Services. This Policy applies to all Bezar applications and services used by you whether your use is on a computer, mobile device, tablet or other platform. By using or accessing the Site or the Services, you acknowledge and accept the practices described in this Policy.

## Information Collected

During the registration process, we collect personal information such as your name and email address. Once you complete and submit your registration, you have opted in to receive email communication from us. We also collect personal information when you choose to use certain other features of the Site. For example, when making purchases, we require you to provide additional personal information, such as your phone number, billing and shipping addresses, and credit card information. We may request additional personal information such as your shopping preferences and demographics.

In addition, through the Site, we automatically gather certain information about the use of the Site, such as how frequently certain areas of the Site are visited, including through the use of cookies, web beacons and other technologies. This gives us valuable information about your customer shopping experience and is used only to improve your experience with our Site. Most browsers can be set to prevent cookies or to notify you when one is being placed. If you choose to remove or reject cookies, this could affect the availability and functionality of our Services.

If you choose to invite an individual to join our Site, you will need to provide his/her email address. Bezar stores this information to confirm qualifying orders attributable to your account and to track the results of the invitation referrals.

## How We Use Your Information

We use your personally identifiable information to support and enhance your use of the Site and its features, including without limitation: fulfilling your order; providing customer service; tracking email invitations you send; and otherwise supporting your use of the Site. We may also track your past purchases to provide you with a personalized profile of your shopping history. In addition, we may notify you about new services or special promotional programs, or send you offers or information.

The personal information you provide to us will also be added to our databases and used for future communications regarding product offerings or other special promotions. If you wish not to receive these emails you may remove yourself from our list by following the instructions at the bottom of each e-mail. By registering with Bezar, you are automatically subscribed to our email, but may choose to opt out of our email list at any time.

We may permit certain trusted third parties to access your information in connection with their performance of services to maintain and operate the Site and certain features on the Site. For example, we may use third parties to host the Site, operate various features available on the Site, send emails, analyze data, provide search results and links and assist in fulfilling your orders.

To provide services you have requested, it may be necessary to provide your personal information to Bezar merchants and or service providers in order to aid redemption of services requested. Logistics services may utilize supplied information only for completing your delivery.

We may transfer personally identifiable information as an asset in connection with a proposed or actual merger or sale (including any transfers made as part of an insolvency or bankruptcy proceeding) involving all or part of our business or as part of a corporate reorganization, stock sale or other change in control.

We reserve the right to disclose information in order to comply with a subpoena, court order, administrative or governmental order, or any other requirement of law, or when we, in our sole discretion, believe it is necessary in order to protect our rights or the rights of others, to prevent harm to persons or property, to fight fraud and credit risk reduction.

We use non-personally identifiable information in the aggregate, so that we can improve the Site and for business and administrative purposes. We may also use or share with third parties for any purpose aggregated data that contains no personally identifiable information.

Additionally, we may provide links to websites controlled by third parties. We have no control over these websites and our privacy policy does not apply to these third party websites. Please consult the privacy policy of the website you are visiting.

## Security

We are committed to protecting the information we receive from you. We follow reasonable technical and management practices to help protect the confidentiality, security and integrity of data stored on our system. While no computer system is completely secure, we believe the measures we have implemented reduce the likelihood of security problems to a level appropriate to the type of data involved.

Bezar takes reasonable measures to help protect information about you from loss, theft, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction. All orders are transmitted over secure internet connections using SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) encryption technology. In addition, only those employees and third parties who need access to your information in order to perform their duties are allowed such access.

## Children's Privacy and Parental Controls

We do not solicit any personal information from children. If you are not 18 or older, you are not authorized to use the Site. Parents should be aware that there are parental control tools available online that you can use to prevent your children from submitting information online without parental permission or from accessing material that is harmful to minors.

## Changing or Deleting Your Information or Settings

You may update, correct or delete information about you at any time by logging into your online account or sending an email with your request to info@bezar.com. If you wish to deactivate your account, please email us at info@bezar.com, but note that we may retain certain information about you as required by law or for legitimate business purposes. We may also retain cached or archived copies of information about you for a certain period of time.

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our Privacy Policy for the Site, we will post the revised Privacy Policy here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information and whether we may disclose it to anyone. Your continued use of the Site indicates your assent to the Privacy Policy as posted.

## Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at:  
Bezar  
560 Broadway, Suite 201  
New York, NY 10012  
info@bezar.com  

© 2015 Bezar, Inc. All Rights Reserved.
